Good morning, Master Henderson.
Good morning, sir.
Would you like some tea, as well?
Yes, I'd love some.
It's been a while since you were in
charge of the grade school kids.
How are the kids this year?
I must say, they show promise.
I heard you had to give one of them
a Tonitrus Bolt on their first day.
True, it was a rather rare occurrence
for our prestigious Eden College.
It's the first time I've heard
of it happening, too.
I only did what was necessary.
Good deeds shall be praised,
and misconduct will be met with punishment.
That is essential to education.
I have much to learn from you, sir.
As the elementary students pass
through the gates of Eden College
to learn true elegance every day,
our school's traditions shall live on.
Our house of learning exists to ensure
the future of our country is elegant.
Lord Damian!
Isn't this your older brother, Lord Damian?
Yes...
This must be his entrance ceremony!
He's probably elsewhere in this book, too!
Oh, there he is!
Ooh!
There he is again!
And here! He's truly an MVP!
Your brother is just raking in
the Stellas! How magnificent!
But I'm sure you'll become an Imperial
Scholar even faster, Lord Damian!
We all know you'll be the first
to get a Stella in our grade!
W-Well, yes.
But we still have a while until our exams.
Your first opportunity will be...
Our P.E. class next week.
We'll be having a dodgeball tournament
with the other classes!
My friend told me something he
heard from his friend in Class 7.
He said if you become MVP,
you can get a Stella!
Really?
This is your chance, Lord Damian!
MVP, eh?
It is a clear, sunny day.
Young ladies and gentlemen of Eden,
you will be adding another page
to Eden's history today...
Elegantly and brilliantly.
Shut up! You picked a fight with me first!
Anya didn't do anything wrong!
Exactly! First off, you—
Shut up, uggo!
Excuse me?!
Shithead.
Shut it, Stubby Legs!
You're not supposed to talk to girls like that!
Ele...gant.
I have returned!
Welcome home, Miss Anya.
Papa, I have acquired important news!
What?
You may be able to get a Stella
at your next P.E. class?
That's what Becky said.
My friend told me something she
heard from her friend in Class 7.
The MVP from the winning
class in next week's tournament
will receive a Stella!
So it's a rumor? That seems dubious.
Then we need to train, Miss Anya!
Training!
So what sport will you be playing?
Dodgeball.
Dodgeball...
That's the game where you hit your opponent
with a ball to do them in, right?
"Do them in"?
Mama! Teach me a killer move!
Very well! I shall teach you the
ultimate killer move with a ball.
Are you also athletic, Yor?
Oh, not exactly.
I just used to play catch
with my brother sometimes.
I can't tell them I rip people apart
and toss them around on a daily basis!
Just leave this to me, Miss Anya!
I'll show you a killer move that
will help you catch that star!
I will reach for the stars in dodgeball!
Anya will catch the star!
That's the spirit!
I'm glad she's so motivated... but...
Super Anya will catch the star!
Yes!
We'll start with strength training.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Death-Defying Sit-ups
Five.
Six.
Stamina is crucial, too.
Miss Anya!
Now, listen carefully.
You're not just using your
arms when you throw the ball.
You need to make sure you
step out with your foot,
twist your hips as you shift your weight,
channel all of your strength
into your shoulder, and... throw!
Okay! Now you give it a try!
Oh, Loid.
Visualizing the Game
This is training?
I don't really understand how,
but I did decide to let Yor handle this.
Miss Anya, please wake up.
Hey!
Hah!
Hup!
Slap!
Fwap!
Chwass!
I'm gonna catch that star tomorrow!
I did my best. I survived
Mama's ruthless training.
I even thought up a name for my killer shot.
I'm gonna seize that star!
I'm gonna get lots of stars...
so I can help Papa with his mission!
At least it's clear that you're motivated.
Just make sure you don't hold
Lord Damian back, Stubby Legs.
Second son... and his lackeys.
Why are we playing together with the boys?
Being on the same team
with him is the worst.
Second son... The son of Papa's
target for this mission.
Good things happen if
I become friends with him.
Wh-What are you staring at?!
But he gets really mean,
so I don't like him.
Well, I don't have any time to
waste on a runt like you, either.
A runt?
I'm going to get MVP in this tournament
and be rewarded a Stella.
I need to become an Imperial
Scholar just like my brother.
Otherwise...
Father will never notice me.
Hey, wait, Lord Damian!
Gather round!
Your usual P.E. teacher, Bobby,
is out sick, so I will be his substitute.
Do not forget to be proper
young men and ladies,
and execute the most elegant of plays.
Yes, sir.
We will now begin the dodgeball tournament
between Class 3, Cecile Hall,
and Class 4, Wald Hall.
You may now begin!
THE GREAT DODGEBALL PLAN
Let's show them who's boss, Lord Damian.
You've got this, Damian!
Lord Damian!
We gathered some intel on Class 4!
Good.
In order to be awarded a Stella,
you have to become the MVP.
My enemy...
is him!
In order to defeat Class 4
and win this match, first...
we need to defeat him!
The son of a command major, Bill Watkins.
Bill Watkins (6)
Nice catch, Bill!
What the heck is that monster?!
There's no way he's our age!
It's him...
Bazooka Bill!
Because of his obviously
blessed physique and brains,
he won awards in all kinds of
sports tournaments in kindergarten.
The Monster of Bodam!
Are there even that many
tournaments in kindergarten?!
Wearing glasses right now
is dangerous, old man.
I humbly thank you for your concern,
Damian, son of Chairman Desmond.
But I'll be fine, because that
ball won't be hitting me.
Also...
Any hits above the shoulders don't count.
Enemy positions confirmed.
Airflow, humidity... both good.
Gerf.
Gah.
Four hits.
Wow! Way to go, Bill!
What?!
Is that even possible?!
Don't panic! That was just a fluke!
Oh, that wasn't a fluke.
When I throw the ball...
Every imaginable detail has been calculated.
We're not just talking simulations.
I've trained my body to its limit.
Daddy!
Ah, my son, Bill.
Yes, Daddy?
You will eventually be the hero
of Eden, as well as our army.
Make sure you seize those
Stellas with your own hands.
For the future of Ostania!
Sir, yes, sir!
Yes... my victory is predetermined.
Um, hello?! We'll die if
that actually hits us!
Don't worry. I'll hold back on you women.
Actually, that also pisses me off.
Gurk!
Hit.
That's some mouth you've got on you.
Do you really think we went into
this without a plan, you giant oaf?
You can't win...
at dodgeball all by yourself!
Ow!
You're gonna be the MVP! I just know it!
I'm gonna be the MVP!
Let's do this! Formation G!
Right!
Four hits.
I'm not done yet!
Ultimate...
...Shadow...
...Clone...
...Attack!
Shadow clone, eh?
Now, this is what you call...
a real shadow clone attack!
Lord Damian...
It was an honor to fight by your side.
Emile!
I know all kinds of great
things about you, Lord Damian.
Though I can't remember a single one
right now, I'm sure there was something.
Please win, Lord Damian!
Because you'll always be...
a true MVP in our hearts!
The forbidden... face block!
Emile!
Emile! Hey! Speak to me!
Ewen... you dummy. Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
It's not the end yet...
So don't give up hope.
Yeah. I know. I know!
Once we give up, it's game over—
Damn it! At this rate, we're gonna lose.
I need to find his weakness!
I don't care if the others go down.
I need to somehow survive and stand out!
Second son is a real shithead.
Next up...
we have that little runt over there.
I'm going to aim for... her feet!
Wha—
Hey! He missed! Nice!
Let's get the ball going!
She just...
jumped before I threw the ball!
Take this!
In that case...
I'll aim for her right arm!
Okay, her left!
I guess I'll just have to use my secret weapon!
This throw will suddenly change its course
and nail any opponent scampering about!
Take this!
Homing Slider Shot!
What was that about holding back on women?!
Blorf!
Hit.
That's impossible! She's
reading my every attack!
Who in the world is that girl?!
Hey, not bad...
Heh.
"Dodgeball," of course, stems from "dodge,"
meaning to swiftly move out of the way.
Such elegant evasion!
Anya! Look out for the guys out of bounds!
You dummy! Get up, quick!
You were impressive, but even you
can't dodge from that position!
Die!
The bastard just threw that
ball with everything he has!
It's unfortunate... But in the end,
this is her own fault.
Don't worry. I shall survive
and lead Class 3 to victory.
Hit.
Wh-What are you doing, Lord Damian?!
Oh, no! My chance at MVP!
You protected me?
Huh?
Are you a good guy?
N-N-No!
I was just frustrated that he was
taking out our team left and right,
so I tried to catch it...
Damn it all!
You're the only one left.
It's in your hands now.
The future is in Anya's hands.
Now is the time to unleash my killer shot!
Miss Anya, this is my final lesson for you.
The key to throwing a ball well is to
put your whole body into the throw.
Think of this ball as an arrow of light!
I won't let your death
go to waste, second son.
I'm not dead!
I will avenge you!
That power she had when she knocked me out...
She might just be able to...
I have no idea what's going on,
but this is intense.
Could it be...
The most important thing
is shifting my weight.
The power in my step
and the twisting of my hips
need to go to my widdle hands...
And then my widdle hands... um... um...
Anyway!
Killer Shot!
Star Catch Arrow!
Huh? What?
Huh?!
That's game.
Huh?
Yay! We won!
Now you're definitely
getting that Stella, Bill!
Hm? Stella?
There are no Stella awarded for winning
a mere mini-game in a single class.
Who in the world suggested otherwise?
On the other hand, you had the nerve to yell
something as vile as "die" during the match,
so I have no issue with giving
you a Tonitrus Bolt instead.
Don't worry, Bill! We'll just
try harder next time!
We'll have another chance.
But to think...
Two students who were at odds with each other
worked together to take on this challenge.
Too bad, Anya. But you did great!
This shows that you are worthy of
a Stella, young ladies and gentlemen.
Cheer up!
You can't be serious, you moron!
What was that crappy throw?!
I shouldn't have defended you!
Shock!
What's your problem?
It's not like you hit anyone!
Anya doesn't like you after all.
What did you say, Stubby Legs?!
You're not supposed to say
stuff like that to girls!
Or perhaps not.
You really are a shithead.
Huh?! Say that again!
Everything Mama teaches me is useless.
Yeah!
"STELLA"